Fallmo
Programmed, Arted, and Designed by Ethan Johnson
Built on Unity Version 4.5.3f3
Notes for interaction:
Hold right mouse button to rotate camera. Click on objects to interact. Do not click on objects when you are waiting in between turns or have lost. The first level helps teach how far and given color of block can fall.
Notes for setting up a project in unity:
Several gameobjects serve as informational centers. The Camera Center is an empty gameobject which defines the space of the camera. The Main Camera itself houses the necessary scripts for all of the blocks to function so each block must reference the Main Camera for Next Level Script and Score and Timer script. Two sound sources also exit in the form of WoodSource and RewardSource for the respective sounds.
Confirmed to be pulled from GitHub as fully operational.
Build version 3.0 done on May 12th, 2015
Additional notes:
Don't fall.